Guide to the Charles Edward Clark Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Personal correspondence, memorabilia, family records, 1907-1967; Series VI; 4' (9 boxes)
  - Testimonials & resolutions in honor of C. E. Clark
    - 1963-1966 (Box 134, Folder 12-15)
  - Photographs
    - 1907-1963 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Law School Exams
    - 1920s-1930s (Box 135, Folder 17-20)
  - School and Professional Memorabilia
    - High School and Yale College (Box 135, Folder 21-22)
    - Memorabilia: invitations, programs, etc. (Box 135, Folder 23)
  - Biographical newspaper clippings
    - 1907, 1918, 1928-1939, 1940s, 1950s, 1960s (Box 136, Folder 24-36)
    - undated (Box 136, Folder 37)
    - Obituary newspaper article clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 136, Folder 38)
  - Financial Records
    - Income Tax returns, 1920's (Box 137, Folder 39)
    - Salary increases, 1919-1929 (Box 137, Folder 40)
    - Vouchers, 1947-1963 (Box 137, Folder 41-43)
    - Retirement benefits, 1948-1957 (Box 137, Folder 44-45)
    - Retirement benefits, 1957-1963 (Box 138, Folder 46-48)
  - Family Records
    - Family tree (Box 139, Folder 49)
    - Estate of Pauline C. and Samuel O. Clark, 1936-1947 (Box 139, Folder 50)
    - Estate of Mary D. Clark (Box 139, Folder 51)
    - Mary D. Clark (Box 139, Folder 52)
    - Mary D. Clark: account book (Box 139, Folder 53)
    - Estate of Mary D. Clark Correspondence, 1939-Apr 1940 (Box 140, Folder 54)
    - Estate of Mary D. Clark Correspondence, Apr 1940-Sep 1943 (Box 140, Folder 55)
  - Diplomas and Awards
    - Diplomas and awards (Box 141)
      (oversize)
- Additional material, 1925-1945, undated; Accession 1984-M-002; 0.75; (2 boxes)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Received from Morris Cohen, Law School Library, 1983 Aug 25.
  Papers concerning Clark's World War II activities on the Advisory Board on Just Compensation and National War Labor Board.
  - Advisory Board on Just Compensation and National War Labor Board, 1940-1945, undated (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  - "Little Steel" Case, 1942 July (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Bell Telephone Company, 1942 August 13-19 (Box 1, Folder 8-10)
  - Ohio Bell Telephone Company, 1925 August 25-1943 Jan, undated (Box 2, Folder 11-16)
- Additional material, Circa 1905-1963; Accession 2014-M-012; 0.02; (1 envelope)
  This accession consists of photographs of Charles Edward Clark, as well as newspaper clippings and correspondence.
  - Clippings, 1935-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Circa 1905-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional material, Circa 1939 - Circa 1963; Accession 2017-M-041
  - United States Court of Appeals identification, Circa 1939 - Circa 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)